PATRICK CAMILLO

Systems Administrator

+55 11 971148588



patrick.camillo@outlook.com



patrickcamillo.com

ABOUT ME

Experience in IT infrastructure management and user support. Advanced knowledge of Linux and Windows servers, networks, security and cloud. Intermediate knowledge of PowerShell, Python, JavaScript, and in the Salesforce environment. Native Brazilian Portuguese. I hope to continue working as an infrastructure generalist, obtaining qualifications and certifications in networks, servers, ITSM, SOC, cloud and other related technologies.

EXPERIENCE

INFORMATION SECURITY ANALYST

2022 - current | 9Net Tecnologia

Management of network monitoring and reporting tools (PRTG, Zabbix, Grafana). Working in SASE, ZTNA and DLP environments (Netskope), CDN and WAF (Akamai), switching, routing and firewall for customers in the financial, services, security, health and government sectors. Implementation of projects to improve the environment and infrastructure. Maintenance of servers, computers and network equipment. Documentation of equipment and processes.

SUPPORT ANALYST

2018 - 2022 | TFA Tecnologia

IT management and support for clients with law, accounting and technology firms. Development of robots for process automation (Python, Selenium). Deploying and managing solutions on Windows and Linux servers, from bare metal to cloud (Azure, AWS). Dealing with technology suppliers. N1 and N2 technical support for hundreds of users. Maintenance of servers, computers, and network equipment. Documentation of equipment and processes.

EDUCATION

COMPUTER SCIENCE 2019 - 2024 | Faculdades Metropolitanas Unidas

OTHER COURSES

CCNAV7: INTRODUCTION TO NETWORKS 2024 | Cisco Networking Academy

ADVANCED LINUX FORMATION 2023 | Udemy - Matheus Müller

INSTALLING AND REPAIRING COMPUTER NETWORKS 2018 | Senac SP